UNITE Amalgamated Northeast Regional Joint Board Research Files 6000/021
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Security, Police Fire Professionals of America Int'l Union, Local 500, 2001 (Box 7, Folder 28)
- Solidarity of Labor Organizations, 1998 (Box 7, Folder 29)
- Staff Union- 802 Musicians OUR, 1999 (Box 7, Folder 30)
- Positive Promotions Inc., 2002 (Box 7, Folder 31)
- Props for Today Inc., 1998 (Box 7, Folder 32)
- Roberto Building Maintenance Co., 2000 (Box 7, Folder 33)
- R and C Apparel Corp. (Box 7, Folder 34)
- Retail Stores- South of 14th St, NY (Box 7, Folder 35)
- School Uniforms, 1998 (Box 7, Folder 36)
- Security Guards- NYU/Medical (Box 7, Folder 37)
- Rosa Mexicana (Box 7, Folder 38)
- New York City Representatives (Box 7, Folder 39)
- New Press, 2000 (Box 7, Folder 40)
  7/25/00, Employee Handbook
- Old Williamsburg Candle Corp., 2002 (Box 7, Folder 41)
- Party Rental Ltd., 1985-2000 (Box 7, Folder 42)
- Vacation/Day off Schedule, 2000 (Box 8, Folder 1)
- Web Page, 2002 (Box 8, Folder 2)
- Newsletter, 1999 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  Nor'easter
- Local 169, NYC Companies, 1999 (Box 8, Folder 4)
- Montes Deoca, 1999 (Box 8, Folder 5)
- Navarro, 1999 (Box 8, Folder 6)
- Gloversville District, 2000 (Box 8, Folder 7)
  Solidarity Notes
- Greater Northern District, 1999 (Box 8, Folder 8)
- Upstate, Misc., 1993-1999 (Box 8, Folder 9)
- NLRB Petition for Election, 2000 (Box 8, Folder 10)
- Recognition Agreements/Samples (Box 8, Folder 11)
- NLRB Supervisors: Definition (Box 8, Folder 12)
  Questions for Determining Supervisory Status (Blank)
- NLRB- Representation and Decertification Election and Statistics, 2001 (Box 8, Folder 13)
- Hoffman Plastics- Supreme Court Case, 2002 (Box 8, Folder 14)
- Card Check, NYS- Law, 2002 (Box 8, Folder 15)
- Benefit Plan, 1996 (Box 8, Folder 16)
- SPX, 2000-2003 (Box 8, Folder 17)
  Contains folders labeled: Petition/Unit, Meetings/Chronology, Employees-Spread Sheets, Issues: Union Committee Info, Lit Company, Li Union, Contract Survey, Phone Bank, Pension, Benefits/Policies, Research on Company, Research- Unicore, Anti-UNITE News Articles, SPX Contracts, Xerox
- Blake and Todd, 1999 (Box 8, Folder 18)
  Contains folders labeled: Corresp. and other items, Leaflets, Legal-Court, Legal-NLRB, Notes, Plans, Press, Research, Customers- Reports Materials given to Customers, Supporters
- Laundry Conf., 2001 (Box 8, Folder 19)
- Staff Activities, 2001 (Box 8, Folder 20)
- Salaries, 1998-2000 (Box 8, Folder 21)
- Internships, 2001 (Box 8, Folder 22)
- Staff/Applications, 1999-2001 (Box 8, Folder 23)
- Probe Report, 2000 (Box 8, Folder 24)
- Beepers, 2000 (Box 8, Folder 25)
- Workers Comp D'Herneys (Box 8, Folder 26)
- Immigration Materials, 2000 (Box 8, Folder 27)
- AFL-CIO - Strategic Organizing, 1999 (Box 8, Folder 28)
- Staff Meetings- Upstate, 2002 (Box 8, Folder 29)
- Servicing Assignments (Box 8, Folder 30)
- Staff Meetings- 169, 2001 (Box 8, Folder 31)
- Staff Assignments, 2000 (Box 8, Folder 32)
- Staff Meetings, 2000 (Box 8, Folder 33)
- JOR Music World, 2002 (Box 8, Folder 34)
- Jakes Home Deliverer d/b/q- Jake and Jose Trucking, 1997-2000 (Box 8, Folder 35)
- Kim's Video IV, Inc., 2002 (Box 8, Folder 36)
- M. Aron Corp., 2002 (Box 8, Folder 37)
- Muri-Lu Knitting Mill, 1997 (Box 8, Folder 38)
- Mental Retaliation/Developmental Industr. (Association of Retarded Citizens- ARC) (Box 8, Folder 39)
- Marloo Garment, Inc, 2000 (Box 8, Folder 40)
- New Jersey Organizing, 2000-2005 (Box 8, Folder 41)
  Contains folder labeled: March 5 Workshop
- Cibao- Union UhP's- Neg, 2000 (Box 9, Folder 1)
- UhP- Cibao, 2001 (Box 9, Folder 2)
- UhP's from Cibao- Neg, 2001 (Box 9, Folder 3)
- Textile/Clothing Technology Corporation: Modular Manufacturing, 1995 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  Feb 7-10, '95
- Modular Manufacturing Training Manual, 1996 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  Nov. 22, '96
- Settlement, 1999 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  10/8/99
- Company Counters, 2000 (Box 9, Folder 7)
  9/12/00
- Union Counters and Union Proposals, 2000 (Box 9, Folder 8)
- Back Wages, 2000 (Box 9, Folder 9)
- Company Leaflets, 2000 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  Spanish, 10/12/00
- Rotondo Trucking and Warehousing Inc., 2000 (Box 9, Folder 11)
- Red Creek, 1985-1997 (Box 9, Folder 12)
- Plastic Companies, 1998-1999 (Box 9, Folder 13)
- Information, 1999 (Box 9, Folder 14)
- Drafts: Press Conf., Advertisement, Resolution, 2000 (Box 9, Folder 15)
- Cibao- Misc., Neg notes, Union Contract Proposal, 2000-2001 (Box 9, Folder 16)
- Waste Management Companies, 2002 (Box 9, Folder 17)
  Contains folders labeled: Recycling-Sanitation: General Interest, Binghamton, Utica, Buffalo, Syracuse, Ithaca
- Performance Fabrication, Inc., 1999 (Box 9, Folder 18)
- Northern Healthcare Linen Services- UNITE Contract for Troy Faculty, 2001 (Box 9, Folder 19)
- William B. Morse Lumber Co., 1999 (Box 9, Folder 20)
- Westplex Industries Corp., 1999 (Box 9, Folder 21)
- Turner Bellows Inc., 1998 (Box 9, Folder 22)
- Tomra of North America Inc., 1998 (Box 9, Folder 23)
- Ten Cate Enbi Inc., 1999 (Box 9, Folder 24)
- Seneca Foods Corp., 1998 (Box 9, Folder 25)
- Schenectady International, 1991-1997 (Box 9, Folder 26)
  Contains folder labeled: Independent Union of Chemical Workers
- Tops and Bottoms Inc., 1999 (Box 9, Folder 27)
- XTO (Box 9, Folder 28)
- Xerox Certified Suppliers, 1999 (Box 9, Folder 29)
- USA Relay, 1999 (Box 9, Folder 30)
- Ultre Pet, 2001 (Box 9, Folder 31)
- Tough Traveler, 2001 (Box 9, Folder 32)
  4/3/01, Gazette
- Thermopatch Corp., 1998 (Box 9, Folder 33)
- Syracuse Banana, 2000 (Box 9, Folder 34)
- Specialized Packaging International, Inc., 2000 (Box 9, Folder 35)
- SPX - Corporate Info, 1999 (Box 9, Folder 36)
- NYC Art Stores, 2002 (Box 9, Folder 37)
  Contains folders labeled: A.I. Friedman LP, Art Station Ltd., Lee's Art Shop Inc., Brown Arthur and Brothers Inc., Columbia Omni Corp., Executive Accessories Inc., Woodbridge NJ (Pearl Paint), Plaza Artist Materials Inc., Sam Flax, SoHo Art Materials
- Art Store, 2002 (Box 9, Folder 38)
  Contains folders labeled: Worker List, Cards, Petition, Election, Vote Count, Nery Zambrano, Insurance Benefits, Union Lit, Company Lit, Company Information, Personal Manual
- Mi Sook d/b/a Lee's Market Negotiations, 2001 (Box 10, Folder 1)
- Gallery 169, 2002 (Box 10, Folder 2)
- Uhrect Art Store, 2001 (Box 10, Folder 3)
- Other Contracts, 2000 (Box 10, Folder 4)
- Food Plant Contracts, 1999 (Box 10, Folder 5)
- Great Jones, 2000 (Box 10, Folder 6)
  Contains folders labeled: Great Jones Corresp., Memberships/Reco, Wage and Work Policy Information
- Great Jones Books- Warehouse, 2000 (Box 10, Folder 7)
  Contains folders labeled: Notes, Benefits, Committee Contacts, Great Jones Contract, Great Jones Contracts
- Contract Proposal Sets, 1999 (Box 10, Folder 8)
- Contract Preparation, 1999 (Box 10, Folder 9)
  10/10/99
- Information, 1999 (Box 10, Folder 10)
- Labyrinth Book Store, 1999-2000 (Box 10, Folder 11)
  Contains folders labeled: Corresp., Affiliation Agreement, Meetings, NLRB Election, Company Health Benefits, Local 169 Medical and Dental Benefits, Research- D and B's etc., Incident Notes, Labyrinth- Enrollments
- Lee's Market- Mi-Sook, 1998-2001 (Box 10, Folder 12)
- Costs, 2000 (Box 10, Folder 13)
- Requisitions, 2000 (Box 10, Folder 14)
- Pearl Paint Contract, 2002 (Box 10, Folder 15)
- Chicago, 2002 (Box 10, Folder 16)
- Food Industry/Manuf.- NYC and Upstate, 2001 (Box 10, Folder 17)
- Gallery Meeting, 2002 (Box 10, Folder 18)
- Discipline Warnings, 2001 (Box 10, Folder 19)
- Student Support, 2001 (Box 10, Folder 20)
- 42/52 Warehouse (Box 10, Folder 21)
  Contains Kodak Color Prints
- ULP- Ray Burke, 2001-2002 (Box 10, Folder 22)
- ULP Heather Peterson, 2001-2002 (Box 10, Folder 23)
- Upstate Disposal Inc. (subs. Republic Services), 2001 (Box 10, Folder 24)
- NY Waste Sites, 2001 (Box 10, Folder 25)
- Recycling Plants (Box 10, Folder 26)
- UltrePet- Contract, 2003 (Box 10, Folder 27)
- Waste Disposal Targets/Chronology, 2002 (Box 10, Folder 28)
- Telephone/Computers, 2000 (Box 10, Folder 29)
- Building Repairs and Renovations, 2002 (Box 10, Folder 30)
- Telephone- Upgrade, 2002 (Box 10, Folder 31)
- Building- 33W. 14th St., 2000 (Box 10, Folder 32)
  Contains folders labeled: Notes/Schedule, Plans, Contracts, Hochberg Contract, Janko, Carstel Corp., Construction Bids, Misc., General Conditions, Loan, Bathroom Access, Flooring and Paint Colors, Const. Meetings, Punch List, Office Furniture, AC, Floor plans and Teleplans
- Tower Records (MTS, Corp.), 1999 (Box 10, Folder 33)
- Yale Book Co-op, 2000 (Box 10, Folder 34)
- Aramark- NYU, 2001 (Box 11, Folder 1)
- United Production Workers Local 17-18, 1997-1999 (Box 11, Folder 2)
- Yale Co-op, 2000 (Box 11, Folder 3)
- NJ Malls- Court Decisions, 2000 (Box 11, Folder 4)
- Fifth Avenue Committee, 2002 (Box 11, Folder 5)
- ABC Health Service Registry Inc., 1985-2001 (Box 11, Folder 6)
  Contains folders labeled: Home Attendants Contracts
- Albany Laundries, 2000 (Box 11, Folder 7)
- Cibao- Shop Steward Election, 2001 (Box 11, Folder 8)
  5/3/01, English and Spanish
- Survey Results, 2000 (Box 11, Folder 9)
- Contract Campaign- Union Lit, 2000 (Box 11, Folder 10)
  Spanish
- Miscellaneous, 2000 (Box 11, Folder 11)
- Committee/Notes, 2000 (Box 11, Folder 12)
- Translation Code (Box 11, Folder 13)
- Access (Box 11, Folder 14)
- Cibao- Corresp., 2000-2001 (Box 11, Folder 15)
- Zero Insertion Force Section Eight Inc., 1999 (Box 11, Folder 16)
- Cibao Meat Products, Inc., 2000 (Box 11, Folder 17)
  Contains folders labeled: Recognition/Election Corresp., Notes, Charting, leaflets, Campaign, Committee, Back Wages, NLRB Petition, ULP- Company, Political Effort, Research, Economic Zone for Cibao
- Cibao Proposals, 2000 (Box 11, Folder 18)
- Cibao Proposals, 2000 (Box 11, Folder 19)
- Cibao- NLRB, 1995-2000 (Box 11, Folder 20)
- Misc.- Workers Information, 2000 (Box 11, Folder 21)
- Flores, Cayetano, 2000 (Box 11, Folder 22)
- Cibao- Disciplinary Actions, 2000 (Box 11, Folder 23)
- Work Rules (Box 11, Folder 24)
- Cibao- Neg Misc., 2000 (Box 11, Folder 25)
  English and Spanish, 4/29/00
- Cibao- Contract Survey, 2000 (Box 11, Folder 26)
- Workers Recognition, 2000 (Box 11, Folder 27)
- Cibao- Org. Misc., 2000 (Box 11, Folder 28)
- Cibao- Organizing- Workers Info, 2000 (Box 11, Folder 29)
- Cibao- Customers, Sales, 2000 (Box 11, Folder 30)
- Cibao- OSHA Report, 2000 (Box 11, Folder 31)
- Cibao- Dominican Organizations, 2000 (Box 11, Folder 32)
- Avirex, 1999 (Box 11, Folder 33)
- Andres Style Fashion (Box 11, Folder 34)
  68 35th St. Brooklyn
- Bike Messengers, 2000 (Box 11, Folder 35)
- Park Ave Gourmet- Neg ULP, 2001 (Box 11, Folder 36)
- Park Ave Gourmet- NLRB Election Petition, 2001 (Box 11, Folder 37)
- Park Ave Gourmet: Four J Foods- Corp. name, 1992-2001 (Box 11, Folder 38)
- Park Ave Gourmet- ULP, 2001-2002 (Box 11, Folder 39)
- Blanco Leather, Inc., 2000 (Box 12, Folder 1)
- Citimarkets LLC, 2000 (Box 12, Folder 2)
- Upstate- NLRB Materials, Elections, Petitions, etc., 1990-2001 (Box 12, Folder 3)
- NLRB Elections- Upstate, 1984-1998 (Box 12, Folder 4)
- Targets- NLRB, SIC 23, Apparel and Auto Trimmings, 1997-1999 (Box 12, Folder 5)
- Upstate Colleges (Box 12, Folder 6)
  List of Colleges in Central NY, Buffalo/Rochester, and Albany Areas
- Targets- NLRB, SIC 22, Textiles, 1997-1999 (Box 12, Folder 7)
- Targets- NLRB, SIC 203, Food Processing Plants, 1999 (Box 12, Folder 8)
- Targets- UNICORE, SIC 203, Food Processing Plants, 1999 (Box 12, Folder 9)
- Targets- UNICORE, SIC 7389, Miscellaneous Business Services, 1999 (Box 12, Folder 10)
- Targets- UNICORE, SIC 5670, Retail Stores, 1999 (Box 12, Folder 11)
- Targets- UNICORE, SIC 7210, Laundries and Dry Cleaners, 1999 (Box 12, Folder 12)
- Targets- UNICORE, SIC 5093, Scrap and Waste Material, 1999 (Box 12, Folder 13)
- Targets- UNICORE, SIC 5000, Distribution and Warehousing, Wholesale, 1999 (Box 12, Folder 14)
- Targets- UNICORE, SIC 4212, Local Trucking W/o Storage, 1999 (Box 12, Folder 15)
- Targets- UNICORE, SIC 3842, Surgical Supplies, 1999 (Box 12, Folder 16)
- Targets- NLRB, SIC 38, Surgical Supplies, 1996-1999 (Box 12, Folder 17)
- Targets- UNICORE, SIC 2396, Automobile Trimmings, 1999 (Box 12, Folder 18)
- Targets- UNICORE, SIC 30, Rubber, Plastics, Packaging, 1999 (Box 12, Folder 19)
- Targets- Greater Northern, 1998 (Box 12, Folder 20)
- Targets- NLRB, SIC 42, Local Trucking W/o Storage, 1997-1999 (Box 12, Folder 21)
- Targets- NLRB, SIC 50, Scrap and Waste Management, 1997-1999 (Box 12, Folder 22)
- Targets- NLRB, SIC 56, Retail Stores, 1997-1999 (Box 12, Folder 23)
- Targets- NLRB, SIC 72, Laundry and Dry Cleaners, 1997-1999 (Box 12, Folder 24)
- Targets- NLRB, SIC 7389, Miscellaneous Business Services, 1997-1999 (Box 12, Folder 25)
- Targets- NLRB, SIC 5000, Distribution and Wholesale, 1997-1999 (Box 12, Folder 26)
- Targets- NLRB, SIC 30, Rubber, Plastics, Packaging, 1996-1999 (Box 12, Folder 27)
- Targets- Glove Cities, 1996 (Box 12, Folder 28)
- Residential Care Facilities, 1998 (Box 12, Folder 29)
- Utica List, 2001 (Box 12, Folder 30)
- Rochester Area- Trucking and Warehousing Companies, 2000 (Box 12, Folder 31)
- Syracuse Target List- Plastics, 2000 (Box 12, Folder 32)
- Stationery (Box 12, Folder 33)
- Calendars, 1999-2000 (Box 12, Folder 34)
- UNITE Supply List, 2001 (Box 12, Folder 35)
- Notices, etc., 2001 (Box 12, Folder 36)
- Lower East Side Community Labor Coalition- Benefit Fund., 2001 (Box 12, Folder 37)
- Invoices for Translations, 2000 (Box 12, Folder 38)
- Memos/Corresp., 1999-2002 (Box 12, Folder 39)
- Ultrafab Inc., 1996-1999 (Box 12, Folder 40)
- Williamsburgh/Bushwick- Make the Road by Walking, Inc. (Box 12, Folder 41)
- WBAI Unpaid Staff, 2002 (Box 12, Folder 42)
- TUV Taam Corp., 2001 (Box 12, Folder 43)
- Tracy Evans, 2000 (Box 12, Folder 44)
- Tortilleria Chinantla, Inc., 2001 (Box 12, Folder 45)
  975 Grand St., Brooklyn, NY 11211-2704
- The Korean Association of New York Inc., 1999 (Box 12, Folder 46)
- Labor Religion Coalition, 2002 (Box 12, Folder 47)
- NELP, 2001 (Box 12, Folder 48)
- Nodutdol- For Korean Community Development, 2001 (Box 12, Folder 49)
- Student Labor Coalition, 2001 (Box 12, Folder 50)
  8/30/01
- Tepeyac, 2000 (Box 12, Folder 51)
- Working Family Party, 1999 (Box 12, Folder 52)
- Workplace Project, 1992 (Box 12, Folder 53)
- Requests for Internships, 2002 (Box 12, Folder 54)
- Jean Charles- Temp. Organizer (Box 12, Folder 55)
  Resume
- Bob C, 1999 (Box 12, Folder 56)
- Sandrine Dikanbi- Temp. Organizer, 2002 (Box 12, Folder 57)
- Ed Jofre- Benefits, 2000 (Box 12, Folder 58)
- Intern- Lisa Napolitano (Box 12, Folder 59)
- Jose Schiffino- WFP, 2002 (Box 12, Folder 60)
- Tony Valenti- Dental Claims, 2001 (Box 12, Folder 61)
- Misc. #1, 1996-1999 (Box 12, Folder 62)
- Misc. #2, 2001-2002 (Box 12, Folder 63)
- Misc., 1999-2002 (Box 13, Folder 1)
- Joint Bd Meeting, 2000-2001 (Box 13, Folder 2)
- Joint Bd ARC Organizing Budget, etc., 2001 (Box 13, Folder 3)
- Local 169 Council Meetings and Labyrinth Election, 2001-2002 (Box 13, Folder 4)
  Contains 10 folders labeled: Local 169
- UNITE- GEB, 2001-2002 (Box 13, Folder 5)
  1/02
- Job Posting Information, 2000 (Box 13, Folder 6)
  Contains folder: Interview Organizer (Upstate) Hector Urrutra
- Staff Activities, 1999 (Box 13, Folder 7)
- New England Organizer, 1999 (Box 13, Folder 8)
- Jobs for Justice, 2002 (Box 13, Folder 9)
- Good Jobs NY, 2000 (Box 13, Folder 10)
- Community Association of Progressive Dominicans (Box 13, Folder 11)
- CHRI, 2002 (Box 13, Folder 12)
  Coalition for the Human Rights of Immigrants
- Asian American Advisory Council/Other Asian Org. Translators (Box 13, Folder 13)
  Korean and English
- Police, 1999 (Box 13, Folder 14)
  Contains Photographs of a Korean neighborhood/police
- Mexican-American Workers Day Proclamation, 1999 (Box 13, Folder 15)
- Labor Day, 1999 (Box 13, Folder 16)
- Labor Day, 2001 (Box 13, Folder 17)
- Immigration Issues- Politics, Labor, etc., 2000 (Box 13, Folder 18)
- Chants (Box 13, Folder 19)
- Back Wage Forms (Box 13, Folder 20)
- Rochester Schlegel Organizing Committee, 2000 (Box 13, Folder 21)
- Volunteer Organizing Workshop, 1999 (Box 13, Folder 22)
- Organizing Meeting, 2002 (Box 13, Folder 23)
- Research, 1999 (Box 13, Folder 24)
- NYS Power for Jobs Companies, 1999 (Box 13, Folder 25)
- Organizing Reports, 1998 (Box 13, Folder 26)
- Uni Poly, 1999 (Box 13, Folder 27)
- Johnstown Leather Local 11712, 2000 (Box 13, Folder 28)
- Independent Unions (Box 13, Folder 29)
  List of independent unions
- Henry St. Settlement (Box 13, Folder 30)
- Healthy Pleasures, 2000 (Box 13, Folder 31)
- Garden of Eden, 2000 (Box 13, Folder 32)
- Gold Water Enterprises, 1999 (Box 13, Folder 33)
- Federal Business Products, Inc./Federal Direct, 2001 (Box 13, Folder 34)
- Eileen Fisher, 1999 (Box 13, Folder 35)
- Contracting Shops, 1999 (Box 13, Folder 36)
- Citterio, 2002 (Box 13, Folder 37)
- Brgley Manufacturing Co./ NOITU, 2000 (Box 13, Folder 38)
- Park Ave Gourmet- Affidavits Duplicates, 2001 (Box 13, Folder 39)